<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sayesha Aravapalli</title>
    <link>https://Asayesha.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sayesha Aravapalli</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 18:56:13 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://Asayesha.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Organically DevOps: Building Quality and Security into the Software Supply Chain at Liberty Mutual</title>
      <link>https://Asayesha.github.io/publications/alldaydevops/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Asayesha.github.io/publications/alldaydevops/</guid>
      <description>This talk looked at Liberty Mutual’s transformation to Continuous Integration, Continuous Delivery, and DevOps. For a large, heavily regulated industry, this task can not only be daunting, but viewed by many as impossible. Often, organizations try to reduce the friction through micro-fixes, but Eddie’s team asked how to change the culture to reduce the friction and concluded with the following final points:
 Don’t mandate DevOps. Give employees the chance to master their discipline with examples to set and follow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forcing Visits to use SSL</title>
      <link>https://Asayesha.github.io/blog/force-ssl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 14:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Asayesha.github.io/blog/force-ssl/</guid>
      <description>Intro Doesn&#39;t matter whether it&#39;s a CakePHP app for a client, your own personal CMS, or any other web based application. If your passing around passwords or other sensitive info you should really implement SSL. SSL provides 2 main perks to your visitors.
 First it encrypts all communication that flies across the web. This prevents curious or devious billies from getting your secrets. Secondly it ensures to the user that your server is in fact who it claims, and not a nasty &amp;lsquo;man in the middle&amp;rdquo; attack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Analytics</title>
      <link>https://Asayesha.github.io/projects/projects/1google-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Asayesha.github.io/projects/projects/1google-analytics/</guid>
      <description>A consulting project for a Dallas based start-up to understand customer base. The goal of this project was to help the management understand where to allocate their resources to increase their current customer base. Additionally, it was attempted to advise management on its consideration to invest in google analytics 360 as an analysis platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instagram Engagement</title>
      <link>https://Asayesha.github.io/projects/projects/3instagram-engagement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Asayesha.github.io/projects/projects/3instagram-engagement/</guid>
      <description>Considering that in 2014 social users posted an average of 1.8 billion photos to the internet daily and the growth of image-centric platforms like Instagram, Snapchat and Pinterestmakes analyzing visual data also very important to understand your audience. Using data scraped form the Instagrampage of Natgeo, this project answers the question What should National Geographic do to increase engagement on its Instagram page?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recommendation Engine</title>
      <link>https://Asayesha.github.io/projects/projects/2book-recommendation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Asayesha.github.io/projects/projects/2book-recommendation/</guid>
      <description>Today in the world of personalized marketing, it is important to understand each customer and target them accordingly. The task of analyzing customer behaviour from humongous is a challenging one and this project attempts to recommend books to users based on their given ratings of other books. The dataset used is Goodreads book rating data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search Results</title>
      <link>https://Asayesha.github.io/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Asayesha.github.io/search/</guid>
      <description>This file exists solely to respond to /search URL with the related search layout template.
No content shown here is rendered, all content is based in the template layouts/page/search.html
Setting a very low sitemap priority will tell search engines this is not important content.
This implementation uses Fusejs, jquery and mark.js
Initial setup Search depends on additional output content type of JSON in config.toml
[outputs] home = [&amp;quot;HTML&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;JSON&amp;quot;] Searching additional fileds To search additional fields defined in front matter, you must add it in 2 places.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>